toneitup.com 2019-05-24

# Tone It Up Privacy Policy - ToneItUp.com

**Tone It Up Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective on September 1, 2017

**General  **

This Privacy Policy describes the practices that Tone It Up, LLC (referred to hereinafter as “Tone It Up” or “we”) follows with respect to the collection, use, maintenance and disclosure of information collected through the website at ToneItUp.com and the Tone It Up software application (collectively, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect from the Service, and does not apply to any other website or business activity of Tone It Up. By using our Service, you consent to the collection, use, maintenance and disclosure of this information by us.

We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time. When we do, we will give you notice of the revised Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Service and by revising the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the current privacy policy.

**Information We Collect & Technology Used **

We collect “personally identifiable information” and “usage information”.

“Personally identifiable information” is information that tells us who you are, such as your name, physical address, and e-mail address. “Usage information” is information automatically collected by our web server (which may be hosted by a third-party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit or use our Service, such as your computer’s IP address or browser type.

We may collect **personally identifiable information** when you create an account with our Service, edit or update your account information or profile, make a purchase, participate in certain activities via the Service, or if you voluntarily choose to provide it to us (e.g., by posting it on the Service). For example, we may collect your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number and geographic location.

You can choose not to provide personally identifiable information to us. However, if you do not provide certain information (e.g., name and email address), you will not be able to create an account so your ability to use the Service will be limited to those web pages available to unregistered users of the Service, and you will not be able to purchase products from us or purchase a subscription to our Service. Additionally, most browsers can be configured to reject cookies or alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, it is possible that some portions of the Service may not function as intended.

We may collect **“usage information”** anytime you view and/or interact with our Service or its pages, features and functionality. For example, we may collect your IP address, browser type, operating system version, and information regarding your geographic location and browsing activities (e.g., information about the website that you visit before or after visiting the Service).

We may also collect information about the **activities** (e.g., fitness classes) that you participate in, and the amount of time that you spend on each activity, and provide that information to Apple’s HealthKit as set forth below.

This Service may also use **“cookies” and other technologies** to recognize users, customize their experience or serve advertisements. A cookie is a small text file that a website’s server places on a user’s computer, mobile phone or other device. The cookie transmits information back to the website’s server about the browsing activities of the computer user on the site. This includes information such as pages and content viewed, the time and duration of visits and whether a computer user clicked on an advertisement. Cookies also can be used to recognize users and maintain data related to a particular individual, including passwords.

In some contexts, such as where a number of separate websites participate in a network, cookies and other technologies can be used to track a computer user across different sites.

As important as cookies are to our Service, we understand that this might make you uncomfortable. If you would prefer not to accept cookies from our Service or any other website, you can modify the settings on your web browser. You may refer to your browser’s online help feature or user manual for instructions on how to do this. If you refuse to accept cookies, it is possible that some portions of the Service may not function as intended.

In some instances, personally identifiable information and other usage information may be **collected via a third party service provider**. Those third party service providers will provide the personally identifiable information that is collected to us. Such information will be subject to our privacy policy but may also be subject to the third party’s own privacy policies. For example, we may use cookies (as discussed above) through Google Analytics. **For more information on collection and processing of data through Google Analytics, please see www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.  **

**Disclosure and Use of Information We Collect  **

We use **personally identifiable information** for the purpose for which it is provided and for the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use personally identifiable information to fill, confirm and ship your order and notify you of your order status; to communicate with you about the Service and for marketing and promotional purposes; to respond to inquiries; to provide customer support; to establish your online account and/or subscription to the Service; and to promote our Service and share information about our users’ experiences with others.

Certain information that you provide will be publicly available on the Service. For example, other users of the Service will be able to see information that you include in your public profile, information regarding your participation in classes offered via the Service, and geographic location.

We may also disclose certain personally identifiable information publicly if we choose to use such information for advertising and marketing purposes. For example, we may use your name and other content that you submit (including photographs and text) in advertisements that are publicly disseminated (online or elsewhere).

We may provide your personally identifiable information to our suppliers who will deliver your order and/or provide billing services, and to third parties who provide services to us.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, our parent company and sister companies.

We use **usage information** to help us run and maintain our Service, customize the visitor’s experience, study traffic patterns, service our online community, generally learn about the usage of the Service and provide a more seamless experience on the Service. We may disclose this information to our affiliates and third parties, including, but not limited to, our advertisers.

Depending on your settings, we may also provide certain **fitness information** to third parties who operate other software applications that interface with ours. For example, we may provide information about your fitness activities (e.g., the activity that you participate in and the duration of your participation) to Healthkit, which is operated by Apple and allows you to view such information via the Health app. We may also use such information in aggregate form for purposes of data analytics.

We use cookies to maintain information about your use of our Service, help us recognize you when you visit our Service again, identify the website you visited immediately before visiting our Service, and enable us to evaluate and improve our Service design.

We may **use and disclose personally identifiable information and usage information** when we have reason to believe that using and/or disclosing this information is necessary to investigate, identify, contact, or take action against someone who may have engaged in illegal activities or breached our Terms & Conditions of Use or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Service, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it.

We might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, personally identifiable information and other information generally are transferred business assets but remain subject to the applicable Privacy Policy. Also, in the event that our assets are sold, personally identifiable information and other information may be transferred assets.

**Advertising  **

We may tailor advertisements on the Service and elsewhere to a user’s apparent interests, based on that user’s online activity. That is, ads may be displayed for you online based on the pages and content that you view.

**Privacy of Children  **

The Service is a general audience website. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from users of this Service who are under the age of thirteen.

**Updating Your Information  **

If you would like to review and/or request changes to any of your personally identifiable information collected through the Service, you may do so through your user account, or by contacting customer service via the contact information below.

**Security  **

Information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet is not 100% secure. As a result, we do not ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such information. We will not be responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

You help to maintain the security of your personally identifiable information stored in our systems by keeping your username and password confidential and protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Links to Other Websites  **

While you are using this Service, you may be linked or directed to other third party sites outside of the Service that are beyond our control. Each of these third party sites may have a privacy policy different from ours. For example, you might click on a link or banner ad that will take you off the Service. These links and banners may take you to sites of advertisers, sponsors and co- branding partners. Please review the privacy policies of these sites. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

**Contact Information  **

Please send any concerns regarding our privacy policy to:

**Tone It Up, LLC.** **  
**

**703 Pier Ave.** **  
****Suite B, # 806** **  
**

**Hermosa Beach, CA 90254  **

**1-800-613-9059  **
